The Guide to the Jerome Charyn Papers 1937-1997 MSS.044
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Photographs
  - Portraits - by Marie Ringwald - 1 of 2 - 3 photos, 1969; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Portraits - by Marie Ringwald - 2 of 2 - 4 photos, 1969; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Portraits - by Layle Silbert - 1 photo, 1985; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Portraits - from Michelle Lapautre Agency - 9 photos, 1988; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Portraits From Modernage Custom Darkrooms - 3 photos, 1979; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Portraits - with Black Hat - 11 photos, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Portraits - Viking Press - 3 photos, 1969; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Rose - 3 polaroids, 1978; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Table Tennis Association - 1 photo + Enclosures, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Woolf, Michael - 2 photos, 1981; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Unidentified, undated; 31142040612403 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Series VII: Periodicals
  - Subseries A: Works by Charyn
    - A Suivre, Nos 133-138- Charyn/ Boucq - "Bouche du diable", 1989; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - A Suivre, Nos 150-152- Charyn/ Loustal - "Les Freres Adamov", 1990; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - A Suivre, No. 228 -230 - Charyn/Munoz - "Le Croc du Serpent", 1997; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Air France, No. 4, "Citoyen Sidel", 1997; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Antaeus, No.20, 1976; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Armchair Detective, Vol. 17 - "Blue Eyes and the Barber King", 1984; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Canal BD Magazine #13- "Graine de Gal" White Sonya), 2000; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Carnet #4- "NYC Mafia", 2000; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Comic Art, No. 72 - Charyn/Frezzato - "Bocca del Diavolo", 1990-1992; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Commentary, Vol 35 no 3, Vol 36 no 1 - "Faigele the Idiotke", "On Second Avenue", 1963; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Esprit, No. 216 - "Bartleby dans le Bronx", 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Freibeuter, No 4 - "Harvey", 1980; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gang No. 1 - "Le ver et le Solitaire" + review, 1979; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Geo, No. 223, "Moi, Charles Henschke, di Einstein" (????)), undated; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Globe, No 32 - "Les Enfants de Chappaquiddick", 1988; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Graat, No. 12 - "Desperately seeking of the "Undersong" ", 1994; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Heavy Metal Overdrive, Vol. 9, No. 1 - Charyn/Frezzato, "Margot, Queen of the Night", 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Le Chroniqueur, No. 3 - "Goliath" + Enclosed letter, 1997; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Le Nouvel Observateur, "Paris, New York, and John Cooper Powys", No 836, 1980, 1991; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Les Inrockuptibles, No., 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - L'ment #22- "Scorsese: Dernier Cauchemar ew York,", 2000; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - L'Europeen, No. 1, "Mon Bled a moi", 1998; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - L'Express Paris, "La cite de tous le seins, par Jerome Charyn", Apr. 2, 1984-1997; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Liberation, Le Magazine, Nos 1, 6-8, 10 - "Z'Yeux Bleus dans les Villes", 1994-1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Liberation, Le Magazine, Nos 11-13,15,16,18-, 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Linea D'Ombra, No. 130, "Il Crime Writer", (1998); No. 136, excerpt from "Morso del Serpente," (1998), 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Lire, # 239, "L'umners d'un ecrivain", 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Los Cuadernos del Norte, No. 51 - "Nuestra Senora de Montegrumo" + Review, 1988; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Magazine Litteraire, No. 341, - "Scott L'insaisissable", 1996; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Merian New York, No 11/40 - "Insel der Tranen", 1988; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Meridiani, No. 2, "L'Isola della Speranza", 1988; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Museart, No. 44 - "Un Americain a Paris", 1994; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Page, No. 37 - "New York en Crize", 1995; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Playboy, No. 32 - "Le Tueur en Culottes Courtes", 1988; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Schwer Metall, Nos. 156-160 - Charyn/Frezzato - "Margot in Badtown", 1992; 31142040613617 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Tempetes sous un Crane, No. 7, "De New York au Polar", 1995; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Torpedo, No. 2 - "Rapporto Sul Crimine", 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - TWA Ambassador - "Centers of Civilization: New York City", Oct., 1986; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - UNESCO Courier, Basque edition- "Mosorropean", 1993; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - UNESCO Courier, "New York Blues", (1997), - 1 of 2 (8 issues in different languages), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - UNESCO Courier, "New York Blues", (1997) - 2 of 2 (7 issues in different languages), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - USA, No. 48/49 - Charyn/Gillard - "Brother John", 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - USA, Nos. 51-56 - "Margot in Badtown", 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - USA, Nos. 57-67 - "Margot in Badtown", 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - VSD, No. 792 - "Attention, le Chaudron Pourrait Exlposer", 1992; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Subseries B: Works about Charyn
    - American Journal, No 1 / 4 - "The Tar Baby" review, undated; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Art and Culture - Alain Delanois, "Le Petit Theatre de Charyn", (May 1996), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - L'Arche, No. 446 - Antoine Spire, "Le voyon du Chaos"/ Myriam Anissimov "L'Universite de la rue", 1994; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - L'Autre Journal, No. 28 - Eric Libiot, "Jerome Charyn et Daniel Pennac...", 1992; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Critique no. 356 - Pierre-Yves Petillon, "The Tar Baby", 1977; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - DC Comic Editorial Presentation - "Family Man", 1994; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Epok - interview and excerpt from White Sonya, 2000; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - L'Express - Sylviane Pasquier "La fourrure du cameleon", Oct 21-27 1988; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - L'Express - Interview with Charyn by Sylviane Pasquier and enclosed note, 9/25-10/5 1994; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper article in Greek, undated; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Fnac Agenda - Cecile Block-Rodot "Jerome Charyn, 1994; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Het Spectrum - "Een Curieuze Cocktail...", 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Hor Jeu - Interview, Sept. 1989; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Les Inrockuptibles no. 35- Samuel Blumenfeld "Main basse sur la ville", May 1992; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Le Nouvel Observateur no. 791- Jean-Claude Zylberstein "Charyn chez Joyce", 1980-1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Lire au College no. 42 - Robert Briatte "Documentaire", undated; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Magazine Litteraire no. 281 - Marc Chenetier, Review, 1990; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Museart no. 36 - Emmanuel Dayde, "Black Charyn", 1993; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The New Reader, v.1,n.2 - Alex Waterhouse-Hayward "The Vampire of Paris and Manhattan...", 1996; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Polar n. 15 and 18 - Dossier: Jerome Charyn", 1995, 1997; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Revue Pretexte n.3 - Interview, reviews and enclosures, 1995; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Saturday Review, American Scrapbook review, 7/23/1969; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Sette Corriere della Sera n.2 - Laura Grimaldi "La Vendetta di Pinocchio", 1996; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Telegrama n.2456 - Martine Laval "Ma Mere, ce Heros", undated; 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous Periodicals
    - A Suivre, Nos 142, 145, 151 (1989-1990), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - A Suivre, Nos 166, 200 (1991-1994), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - A Suivre, Nos 201, 219, 227 (1994-1996), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Ararat, No. 32, (incl. "Last One Home", by Marlene Charyn), 34, (1968), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - The Atlantic Monthly (Nov. 1977), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Cahiers du Cinema, No. 143/44 (1991), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Today (Fall 1977), 31142040613625 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Columbia College Today, 1968-1970; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Columbia College Today, 1971-1991; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Commentary, No 37/3, 1964; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Diamond World Review No. 1 (1975), 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - L'Evenement Du Jeudi, n. 375, 1992; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Le Figaro n.13757, 14116, 1988, 1990; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Fnac Agenda, OCt 1991, May/June 1994; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Folio n.3,5,6, 1993; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Giono: Magazine Litteraire n.75, 1973; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Graffiti n.44, 1994; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Le Grand Livre du Mais and enclosures, Nov. 1991, Feb. 1993; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Les Inrockuptibles, Nos. 32, 57, 1991,1994; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Spectator, v.30 n.8, 1965; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Jubilee, 1962; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Mademoiselle, Apr. 1964, Sep. 1965; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Il Maltese, 1992; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Marie Claire, n.436, 1988; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Midstream, n.16/4, 1970; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - The New Leader v.53 n.21, 1970; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - The New Republic, 1967-1979; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - New York, 1970-1978; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - New York, 1980; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - New York, 1980; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Newsweek, Jun 9, 1969, Mar. 13, 1972; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Les Nouveaux Cahiers, no.61, 1980; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Paris Match, November 1988; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Playboy, Oct. 1975; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Le Point no. 887, 1989; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Politeia, no.6/2, 1969; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Publishers Weekly, v.184 n.25, 1963; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Quest nos 1/4, 3/5, 11977, 1979; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Realities, n.3, 1939; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Revue Pretexte, no.1, 1994; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Sapristi n.33, 1996; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Saturday Review, 1965-1969; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Telegrama n.2095, 1990; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Tennis de Table n.602, 1990; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Time nos. 94/1, 112/18, 1969, 1978; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Tavelaide, 1978, 1979; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Vogue, Dec. 1990, Sep. 1991; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Vogue, Feb 1996; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - VSD no.619, 1989; 31142040613633 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Series VIII: Newspapers
  - Subseries A: Clippings
    Box 13
    - Articles about Charyn - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Articles about Charyn - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Articles by Charyn - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Articles by Charyn - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - American Scrapbook - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - American Scrapbook - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The Catfish Man - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - The Catfish Man - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Catfish Man - Source Materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Darlin' Bill - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Darlin' Bill - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - The Franklin Scare - Reviews, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Going to Jerusalem - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Going to Jerusalem - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Going to Jerusalem - Source materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Isaac Quartet - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Isaac Quartet - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - King Jude - Source Materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - La Paresse - Reviews, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - A Man Who Grew Younger - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - A Man Who Grew Younger - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Marylin the Wild - Source Materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Reviews, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Source Materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - On the Darkening Green - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - On the Darkening Green - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Once Upon a Droshky - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Once Upon a Droshky - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Reviews in Italian, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - The Seventh Babe - Reviews, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - The Tar Baby - Reviews - Copies, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - The Tar Baby - Reviews - Originals, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Viking Press, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Werewolf or Magician's Wife - Source Materials, undated; 31142040613641 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Subseries B: Newspapers
    Flat Box 1; Flat Box 2
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 9-Jul-91, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 9-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 10-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 11-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 12-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 13-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - A Quemarropa (Associacion Semana Negra): 14-Jul-94, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Book Week: 18-Apr-1965, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Book Week: 09-Sept-1965 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Book Week: 23-Apr-67, undated (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Book Week: 12-Feb-1967 (Includes "Arthur Miller off Stage", by Charyn) (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Fiction: Spring 1972 (includes "Galapagos") (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Fiction: Fall 1972 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Fiction: Vol 1, No. 3, 1972 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Fiction: Vol 2, No. 1, 1973 (includes "Paparinemo" from A Child's History of the Bronx) (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Fiction: Vol 2, No. 2, 1973 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Figaroscope: September 27, 1995 (includes "Jerome Charyn, un enfant dans la ville" by Marie-Ange Poyet) (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Frankfurter Rundschau: No. 92/16, April 20, 1995 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - La Tribune: July 17-25, 1995 (includes "Jerome Charyn ..." by Thierry Gadault ) (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 120, July 19, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 123, July 22, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 124, July 23/24, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 126, July 26, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 128, July 28, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 130, July 31, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 132, August 2, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 134, August 4, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 136, August 6/7, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 137, August 8, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 138, August 9, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 140, August 11, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 141, August 12, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 142, August 13/14, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 146, August 18, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 147, August 19, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 148, August 20/21, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 149, August 22, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Matin: No. 150, August 23, 1977 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Monde: No. 13614, November 4, 1988 (includes "Jerome Charyn ou l'ombre de l'arpernteur" by Daniel Pennac) (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Le Monde: No. 16006, July 13, 1996 (Box Flat 1, Folder loose)
    - Liberation;: No. 1723, August 25/26 1979, (Includes "Coen Amoreux") (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation;: No. 1789, Novermber 11, 1979, (Includes "Harvey") (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation;: No. 1790, November 12, 1979, (Includes "Charyn, le dingue in Paris" by Michel Martens) (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation;: No. 2004, July 27, 1980, (Includes "Un geek a Paris", by Charyn and Michel Martens) (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2006, July 28, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2007, July 29, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2011, August 2/3, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2012, August 4, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2013, August 5, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2015, August 7, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2016, August 8, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2017, August 10, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2019, August 12, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2020, August 13, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2021, August 14, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2023, August 16/17, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2024, August 18, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2025, August 19, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2027, August 21, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2029, August 23/24, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2030, August 25, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2031, August 26, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2032, August 27, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2034, August 29, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 2327, November 12/13, 1988, (includes "Zyeux-Bleus revient", by Gerard Meudal) (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): No. 4138, September 8, 1994 (includes "L'humeur Charyn", by Gerard Meudal ) (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): Livres, 1992 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - Liberation; ("Arnold, le geek de New-York", by Charyn and Michel Martens): Les Auteurs Liberation, March 19, 1998 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - New York Arts Journal;: No. 22, 1981 (includes "Harvey") (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - The New York Review of Books;: Vol. IV, No. 6, March 22, 1965 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - The New York Review of Books;: Vol. XXV, No. 10, June 15, 1978 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - The New York Review of Books;: Vol. XXV, No. 13, August 17, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
    - The New York Review of Books;: Vol. XXVII, No. 4, March 20, 1980 (Box Flat 2, Folder loose)
- Series IX: Typescripts and Galleys
  - 1944 - Edited Typescript - 1 of 4, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1944 - Edited Typescript - 2 of 4, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1944 - Edited Typescript - 3 of 4, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1944 - Edited Typescript - 4 of 4, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1944 - Long Version - Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1944 - Typescript - Copy, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1948 + Abortive Poem - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Abandoned Novel - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Abandoned Story (Shim) / Abandoned Novel About Arky - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Afterward - Who is Hyde - typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - American Scrapbook - Assorted Pages and Notes, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - American Scrapbook - Galleys - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - American Scrapbook - Galleys - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - American Scrapbook - Setting Copy, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Back to Bataan - Galleys - 1 of 3, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Back to Bataan - Setting Copy, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - A Bed With a View - Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 17)